Uh, the way you crushed Mike at ping pong
was such a turn-on.
You want to...
You know, I, I'd love to but I'm a little tired.
I'll put a pillow case over my head.
You're on.
Hey / What's up?
Well, Ok, Mike's taking a shower,
which by the way, there is no law against.
And then we're gonna grab some food
so if you want..
...(finally)...
Is that Ross?
Yeah, you can hear everything
through the stupid walls.
Sounds like he's with someone.
He could be alone. This morning I heard him
do push-ups and then talk to his triceps.
Wait a minute. I think Phoebe is right.
Yeah, I hear someone else in there with him.
Dr. Geller.
God, you're amazing.
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
Oh my God! That's Charlie!
She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
Oh, that tart, floozy, Giant!
I'm not sure about this.
Yeah, you..you're right.
This is none of our business.
No, I'm not sure that is the best way
to hear everything. Someone get me a glass!
I'm not gonna do this, Ok?
I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
(Oh, I love Barbados)
Oh, I can't believe I'm kissing you.
I'm kissing Rachel!
I know! I'm her!
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
What?
Get over here!
Whoa!
Oh my God! I love how thin these walls are!
Thank you.
Transcribed by - Kevin Kim
You CAN distrubute this file freely without my permission.
So no one told you that was gonna be this way
Your job's a joke, you're broke,
Your love life's D.O.A.
It's like you're always stuck in 2nd gear.
When it hasn't been your day, your week,
your month, or even your year ....but
I'll be there for you.
when the rain starts to pour
Like I've been there before
I'll be there for you.
'Cause you're there for me...too.
Hey, you know, before, you said that nothing
could happen between us. What changed?
Well, I only said that because of Ross
and then I saw him kissing Charlie.
What?
Ross and Charlie?
Wow! She's really making her way
through the group, huh?
Eh, who am I to talk?
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
How about the dinosaur twins in the other room?
No one is manning that wall.
I'm on it!
Anything?
I think I hear curtain's closing.
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
bed springs! Unmistakable!
You do realize that's your brother.
Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
Wait a minute! Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
Phoebe and Mike. We're the only people
leaving with the same person we came with.
That's not true. I came with Monica
and I'm leaving with 'Weird Al'.
Ok, I've had it with the hair jokes.
Tomorrow morning before we leave,
I'm going to the salon.
Ok, buckwheat.
You, you got to hear this. It's great!
It's, it's like free porn.
Is everything ok?
Yeah, it's just I...I don't think I can do this.
Oh, is it because of what might be under bed spread
cause I saw that news report too
with that infrared and we could just...
No, no, no, no, uh,
Look, I, I need to talk to Joey.
I mean you guys just broke up.
Before anything more happens between us,
I need to know he's okay with it.
I...I completely understand.
Alright, I'm gonna go find him.
I just need a, need a second
before I can...you know
Grandma, grandma,
Okay, I'll see you later. / Ok
That's the door. He's gone.
And she's turning on the TV,
and watching ...
'Miss congeniality'!
Honey, if you know it through a wall,
you know it too well!
Hey, what are you guys doing?
Ah,..we're, we're just sad to go
so we're just saying good bye to the hotel.
I love you.
Paradise hotel. Golf resort and spa.
Yeah, we had a great time. Thank you.
Bye.
Okay. Um, hey, have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
He's probably in his room
with his current girlfriend Charlie.
That's the situation as we know it.
Well, if you see him, could you please
tell him I'm looking for him?
You got it! / Thanks
Thank you.
Other wall, people, other wall!
Rach, you there?
Oh my God! It's Ross. What are we gonna do?
Ok, just , just, be calm, just be calm
for all I know is
we're just, we're just hanging out together.
Alright, let's just be nonchalant.
That's not nonchalant!
No idea what it means!
Oh!
Ok, just hide.
Rach? / Coming.
Try under the bed. Try under the bed.
There's no room under the bed.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Hey / Hi
Do you know where Joey is?
I really don't.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah sure.
I don't believe this!
Have you guys been...? / Shhh.
This is the listening side of the wall.
And then she told me that
she and Joey had broken up, and that
part of the reason was that
she had feelings for me.
Uh-huh. Right. Yeah.
And you know I wanted to ask Charlie out
since the day I met her.
Oh, I know! I know it's been really hard for you.
Anyway, one thing led to another, and
before you know it, we, we were kissing.
I mean how, how angry do you think
Joey's gonna be.
That is hard to say, Ross. That is hard to say.
You know, I've got to go find him.
He's got to be here some place.
You would think!
Joey!
Is he gone?
How are you doing this?
wh..what? Hey!
What are you...what is this?
Have you guys been listening this entire time?
Yeah!
Now but what is this?
What is this? Well, let's see.
We, we kissed for 10 minutes and
now we're talking to our friends about it
so I guess this is the sixth grade!
No, no. Have you thought about
how complicated this could get?
What about Ross?
Well, he's with Charlie now.
Yeah, but he wants to talk to you
before anything really happens with her.
and as his friend I mean don't you think
he deserves the same from you?
You're a pain in my ass, Geller.
Alright, look, you guys, look.
We appreciate all the advice but this is between Joey and me,
and I think we can handle it.
Ok, while we go back in there, but
will you do one thing for us,
the people that care about you? / Sure.
Enunciate!
Get out!
Are they right?
Probably, yeah.
I mean, maybe we should ...
hold off until we talk to Ross.
Yeah, yeah. We can wait.
We don't have to do anything tonight.
Yeah, I think, I think that would be best.
So, so I'm gonna, I'm gonna take off.
although...
I like although!
I mean, you know.
Ross and I haven't dated in like...
six years?
6 years?
Wow! It's almost as long as high school.
Plus, you know he is ...with Charlie, you know.
Absolutely!
He's not thinking about you. / No!
I'm thinking about you.
Yeah.
Let's forget about Ross.
He's forgotten.
Waht's wrong?
Nothing.
Seriously, what is it?
Nothing. It's really...it's nothing.
Come here. Come here.
What's wrong?
Uh, sorry, I just...um,
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
Well, maybe I can help.
Ah, your lips are so soft. Do that again?
-Yeah, we, we need to tak to Ross. Yeah.
-Yeah.
Hey / Hey
You guys are ready to go?
Not quite. Monica's still at the salon
and I'm just finishing packing.
Dude! You're not taking your bible?
You're not supposed to take that.
Besides, it's new testament.
What are you gonna do with it?
Learn about Jesus.
Hey / So... did you talk to Joey?
Oh no, no. I couldn't find him.
I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
Okay, sounds like a good idea.
Dr. Geller.
Stop it.
P...h... D.
You're filthy.
Hey, have you guys seen Monica?
Uh, actually I think she went to the salon.
Oh, yeah, oh, she went to the salon, alright.
Check it out!
Whose day just got better?
Chandler!
Hey. Ahhh....
What do you think?
I think... I think I can see your scalp.
Don't you just love it?
Yeah, yeah.
You've got shellfish in your head.
It's, uh..., it's something.
You go girlfriend!
You've never said that in your life, have you?
Not once. / I thought so.
And listen to this.
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes
... and the ears!
Wow, it's uh...,
it's kinda weird I'm sitting next to Charlie
after we broke up.
Yeah, it's almost as if Air Barbados
doesn't care about your social life.
Look, does someone mind
switching to sit with Charlie?
Oh, I, I mean, I, dude, I spent
the whole conference with Charlie.
I understand.
No, I'll do it.
Wish I could switch with someone.
I really don't want to sit with
Allen Iverson over there.
Um, you know once we're in the air,
and the captain turns off the seatbelt sign,
you feel free to roam about my cabin.
And you should be careful
when checking your overhead bins.
cause items may shift during the...
Aw, you're not good at this.
You don't have to go home tonight, do you?
No, I think I can come over. Saturday, right?
Oh, / What?
Um, I can't, I can't do anything tonight.
Why not?
I have a date.
You have a date?
With who?
Oh, it's... my girlfriend.
You have, you have a girlfriend?
Yeah, ...when you and I broke up,
I started seeing someone.
Whoa, for how long?
3 months. / 3 months?
Ok.
This is probably none of my business but
how long do you think you're gonna keep seeing her?
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner.
I ...I promise.
Oh, okay, good. You do that.
And then when you get home, maybe there'll
be a special delivery package waiting for you.
Maybe I'll sign for it.
Tear it open.
Pull out the packing material.
You know what? We're gonna have sex.
Let's just leave it there.
Alright, I'm gonna go talk to Joey.
I think this is the right time.
He's always in a good mood
after the flight attendant says "duty free".
Okay, good luck.
Ross's coming over. I think
now will be a really good time to talk to him.
Oh, oh, I guess so. I'm just really nervous.
Ok, well, keep in mind that by the time you're done,
they'll probably be serving dinner.
Ooh...
Still nervous?
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
Hey, Rach. / Yeah.
Do you... do you mind if I sit here for a sec?
Yeah. yeah, sure. Yeah.
Hey. / Hey.
So I, um, I kinda need to talk to you about Charlie.
Yeah?
Ok, last night, after you guys broke up,
so sorry to hear about that by the way,
well, Charlie and I were talking and ...well
You kissed.
What? ...What?
What would give you that idea?
I saw you.
Yeah, we kissed
but nothing else nothing else happened, okay?
Ross, Ross, it's okay. / What?
It's okay.
I totally understand now you guys make
way more sense than her and I ever did.
You know? And...
I want you to be happy.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Now I have something....
I AM speechless!
I mean the fact that you would
put my happiness first like that?
I mean you....you are an incredible friend,
you know that?
Look before you go to...
No, no, I mean it.
I mean you're so , you're so loyal man. and, and
selfless and generous.
I am those things, yeah.
You know, I've known Chandler longer
so I always think of him as my best friend.
But now...
I may have to rethink some stuff.
Dude!
Hey, if there is ever anything
I can do for you.
I can't think of anything.
Thanks. / Yeah.
So hi / Hi
So you, uh,..you talked to Joey.
Oh yeah. We had a really good talk.
Oh, that's great! / Yeah.
Oh so everything's okay?
Oh, no, no. It's great! It's great!
He, he's an amazing guy.
Oh,...well, obviously I think so too.
Well, I'm, I'm so excited about this.
Really? Excited?
Oh, what? Are you kidding?
I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
Excuse me.
You didn't tell him, did you?
I couldn't. He was saying
all these really nice things about me.
I didn't want him to get mad
and take'em all back.
I'm gonna edge out Chandler. / Oh God!
Alright, fine. You know what? Joey, forget it.
When we go back to New York, I will tell him.
Thank you, yeah. I appreciate that.
Hi, Mike's place.
Hey, it's Mike.
Ooh, that was fast!
Oh, ah, no, she's not here yet.
You know, I think I'm gonna just take off
and break up with her over the phone.
No, you can't do that!
Oh, come on, Mike. strap on a pair.
Why don't you just tell her
that we got back together?
You know, women appreciate honesty.
We also... appreciate gentle spanking
once in a while . Just FYI.
One more thing. There might be a picture of
"Precious" on my coffee table.
Her name's Precious?
Is she a pure breed or
did you pick her up at the pound?
Anyway, I just want to give you a heads up.
Okay. Oh, and you know if she gets upset,
just scratch her tummy and give her Liva snap.
Hi, I'm Precious. Who are you?
I'm, I'm Phoebe.
Phoebe? Mike's ex-girlfriend Phoebe?
The love of his life? That Phoebe?
Enchante'e.
Oh, I can't wait for everyone at work to see these! Ow!
-You go back to work tomorrow night, right?
-Yeah
So if you want people to see them,
then by definition
you're not having them taken out,
say at the break of dawn?
Well, if I had them taken out then
I wouldn't be able to do this.
You like that, right?
What are you singing?
It's Bolero from "10".
It's "ride of the Valkyrie's"
from apocalypse now.
See, here's the thing. The corn rows are
really a solution for your frizzy hair problem.
And now that we're at home
you don't have that problem any more.
So if you think about it, I HATE them.
What? You said you liked them.
Did I? Let's refresh.
I believe what I said was
that I could see your scalp.
Fine, so you don't like them.
Everybody else does.
Again, let's journey back.
As I recall, what Rachel said was
she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
and Joey...
well, Joey didn't realize
there was anything different.
You know what? I don't care.
I like it like this, and I'm gonna keep it.
And you're just jealous
because your hair can't do this.
Ouch!
Get yourself in the tooth?
And the eye!
Hi, there she is . Hi, Emma. Oh my God.
I missed you. Oh, Emma,
I missed you so much.
Did you have a good time
with grandma Greene? Huh?
Did she give you a bottle of
antidepressants again to use as a rattle?
That was one time, Ross and
they were only like 5 milligrams.
Ooh, hey, Emma,
Daddy has some presents for you, okay? okay?
I want you to wait right here.
Come here, sweetie.
Huh, Ross,um actually there is something
that I really need to talk to you about.
Ok, shoot.
Okay, um, alright, here's the deal.
Oh, no!
What? What is it?
Oh, major shampoo explosion!
Ah, look, Ross, this really isn't easy.
Oh, it's all over everything.
Why? Why me?
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
Well, yeah, ok, it's about me and...
Oh, not another one!
Oh my God! Oh and this is moisturizer.
It's even harder to clean!
Why? Why do bad things happen to good people?
Wow, well, clearly this is not a good time.
Don't you think?
Okay, bye.
Alright so Mike's... on his way over.
You thought you guys were meeting here and
he thought you were meeting at the restaurant.
So you know ...doesn't really matter
who's right or wrong.
The point is... I'm gonna take off.
Wait a minute. I'm not letting you leave
until you tell me what's going on here.
I mean, are you guys
getting back together or something?
Alright.
Susie, can I call you Susie?
My name is Precious.
I can't say that.
Um, Susie, I'm gonna be straight with you.
Mike and I are back together
and um unfortunately that effectively ends
your relationship with him.
And he's very sorry about that and wishes you
the best of luck in all your endeavors.
I just can't believe this.
Why?
Well, I don't ...
Why would he do this?
I mean what's wrong with me?
Nothing. There's nothing wrong with you.
I don't know what the hell am I supposed to do now!
Damn it, woman. Pull yourself together!
Have some pride for the love of God!
Ok, not a fan of the tough love.
I just can't believe that
Mike didn't give me any warning.
But he didn't really know.
You know, he wasn't planning on
coming to Barbados and proposing to me.
He proposed to you?
This is the worst birthday ever!
Look,... Precious.
Mike's not worth this.
You're an attractive, intelligent woman and
let's face it. Mike's kind of a Wang.
I mean he proposed to me
while he was still seeing you.
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
And I don't like to kiss and tell
but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
Oh my God. You know, maybe you're right!
Maybe I don't need him.
I deserve to be treated with respect.
Screw you, Mike. You're a coward and a bastard
and I hope you rot in hell.
You're welcome.
Honey, you've been in there for a long time.
Is everything okay?
Not really.
I have a problem.
Really?
What happened?
Well..., I was dancing around and
singing "no woman, no cry"
and... I got stuck.
You can't move at all?
Oh, I can move.
If I entangle you, will you please
get rid of the corn rows?
I guess so.
Some of these look a little frayed.
Yeah, I tried to gnaw myself free.
Hey / Hi
So did you, uh, did you tell Ross?
Well, I tried
but then he had a shampoo related emergency.
Huh, so I guess now it's your turn again.
No, no, no,....I think it's better
if you tell him. You know?
And it's easier for a woman. That way,
you know, if he gets mad,
all you have to do is go
"I didn't mean it."
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, cause that's what we do.
Alright, alright, okay, um,
how about this? How about this?
Tomorrow,
tomorrow we both go and will tell him together.
Okay, that sounds fair.
That just means, once again, we can't ...
I know, I know. That's okay.
I mean we can control ourselves.
We're not animals. / No!
Of course we can wait.
Alright, so I guess that means good night, then.
Yup. Good night.
Good~ night.
Good night.
Seriously, good night.
Stop saying good night.
Okay!
I'm so sorry.
Look what I found in the drawer.
And you said I would never wear this.
Now that I entangled you,
how about you do a little something for me?
Sure. What do you have in mind?
I think you know.
Really? I don't, I don't really feel like it.
This is what I want to do.
Okay.
I just don't get why you like it so much.
She's an FBI agent posing as a beauty contestant!
THANK YOU. I APPRECIATE YOUR FEEDBACK.
- Kevin Kim